<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<blog_list>
   <blog id="1">
      <title>Rosé</title>
      <category>Singer</category>
      <sortDescription>Roseanne Park, known mononymously as Rosé, is a Korean-New Zealand singer and dancer based in South Korea.</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>Rosé appeared on a variety of broadcast programs, such as King of Masked Singer. Her vocal performance on the show was met with warm reception by the audience, to which Rosé commented that she "didn't know if the audience would like singing" and that she felt "happy and relieved" at the positive result. She later appeared as a performer on the second season of Fantastic Duo. The show's production staff stated that her appearance was intended to "reveal Rosé's vocal appeal, which is different from Blackpink"</longDescription>
      <date>02/01/2021</date>
      <image>img\0.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="2">
      <title>Jisoo</title>
      <category>Singer</category>
      <sortDescription>Kim Ji-soo, known mononymously as Jisoo, is a South Korean singer and actress. She debuted as a member of the girl group Blackpink, formed by YG Entertainment, in August 2016. In December 2021, Jisoo starred in her first role as lead actress in the JTBC drama Snowdrop.</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>Jisoo was ranked as the 10th most popular K-pop idol in 2018 and 17th in 2019 in annual surveys conducted by Gallup Korea. In 2019, she was ranked as the sixth most popular female K-pop idol in a survey of soldiers doing mandatory military service in South Korea. As of February 2021, she is the third most followed K-pop idol on Instagram, along with band member Rosé. In 2019 she was named to the BoF 500, a "definitive professional index" of people shaping the $2.4 trillion fashion industry.</longDescription>
      <date>20/02/2021</date>
      <image>img\1.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="3">
      <title>Jennie</title>
      <category>Singer</category>
      <sortDescription>Jennie Kim, known mononymously as Jennie, is a South Korean singer and rapper. Born and raised in South Korea, Jennie studied in New Zealand for five years before returning to South Korea in 2010. She debuted as a member of the girl group Blackpink, formed by YG Entertainment, in August 2016.</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>Jennie appeared with Blackpink member Jisoo on Running Man in July 2018. A video of Jennie crying after going through a horror room with Lee Kwang-soo went viral in South Korea, gaining over one million views on one site and a total of over three million views across multiple platforms, VODs, and social media. She was subsequently selected as one of the best variety stars of 2018 following her discovery on Running Man. Jennie was invited to the show again after attracting attention during her previous appearance. Jennie was said to have ranked first among casting choices and received multiple offers from different variety shows. On October 1, Jennie was confirmed to join as a cast member for SBS' new variety show Village Survival, the Eight, her first permanent casting in a television series.</longDescription>
      <date>27/03/2021</date>
      <image>img\2.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="4">
      <title>Lisa</title>
      <category>Singer</category>
      <sortDescription>Lalisa Manobal, known mononymously as Lisa, is a Thai rapper, singer and dancer based in South Korea. She is a member of the South Korean girl group Blackpink formed by YG Entertainment. Lisa made her solo debut with her single album Lalisa in September 2021.</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>In August 2016, Lisa debuted as one of four members of South Korean girl group Blackpink, as well as the first non-ethnically Korean to debut under the agency. Blackpink debuted with single album Square One with lead singles "Whistle" and "Boombayah". "Whistle" achieved a perfect "all-kill", topping all South Korean charts upon debut. As of October 2020, the group has released two studio albums, Blackpink in Your Area and The Album, three extended plays, Blackpink, Square Up and Kill This Love, and two single albums, Square One and Square Two.</longDescription>
      <date>24/04/2021</date>
      <image>img\3.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="5">
      <title>IU</title>
      <category>Singer</category>
      <sortDescription>Lee Ji-eun (Korean: 이지은; born May 16, 1993), known professionally as IU (Korean: 아이유), is a South Korean singer, songwriter, and actress. The name IU is a combination of 'I' and 'you' meaning "you and I become one through music." She signed with Kakao M (formerly LOEN Entertainment, now Kakao Entertainment) in 2007 as a trainee and debuted as a singer at the age of fifteen with her first mini album Lost and Found (2008).</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>Although her follow-up albums, Growing Up and IU...IM, brought mainstream success, it was after the release of "Good Day" (Korean: 좋은 날), the lead single from her 2010 album Real, that she achieved national stardom. "Good Day" went on to spend five consecutive weeks at the top position of South Korea's Gaon Digital Chart, and in 2019, it was ranked number one on Billboard's "100 Greatest K-Pop Songs of the 2010s" list.</longDescription>
      <date>16/05/2021</date>
      <image>img\4.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="6">
      <title>Im Yoon-ah</title>
      <category>Singer</category>
      <sortDescription>Im Yoon-ah (Korean: 임윤아; born May 30, 1990), known mononymously as Yoona, is a South Korean singer and actress. After training for five years, she debuted as a member of girl group Girls' Generation (and later its subgroup Girls' Generation-Oh!GG) in August 2007, which went on to become one of the best-selling artists in South Korea and one of South Korea's most popular girl groups worldwide. Apart from her group's activities, Yoona has participated in various television dramas, notably You Are My Destiny (2008), which marked her career breakthrough and earned her the Best New Actress awards at the 23rd KBS Drama Awards and the 45th Baeksang Arts Awards.</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>In March 2012, Yoona was cast in a lead role alongside Jang Geun Suk in KBS2's drama Love Rain, a fantasy drama about fate where the offspring of an ill-fated couple who met in the 1970s, meet and fall in love with each other in the modern era. Yoona played two characters: Yun-hee of the 70s and Ha-na of modern times. Although the drama scored low domestic viewership and was criticized for its failure to relate to the viewers, Yoona's acting received positive reviews. Yoon Ga-ee of OSEN wrote: "The speed at which her acting is improving is blinding. She has matured to the point where you want to ask, 'When did her acting get so good?' The criticism that trailed behind her during Cinderella Man is now nowhere to be found." Choi In-kyung of Hankook Ilbo said her acting was continuously improving and "Yoona is completely immersed in her character and has now become 'Hana' herself." The drama garnered much positive overseas interest and was sold to Japan for $10 million, the second highest price for a KBS drama at the time, partly due to Yoona's popularity.</longDescription>
      <date>15/05/2021</date>
      <image>img\5.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="7">
      <title>Irene</title>
      <category>Singer</category>
      <sortDescription>Bae Joo-hyun (Korean: 배주현; born March 29, 1991), known professionally as Irene, is a South Korean singer, rapper, and actress. She is the leader of the South Korean girl group Red Velvet and a member of its sub-unit Red Velvet - Irene Seulgi.</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>On October 21, 2020, Irene came under fire for mistreating and lashing out at a fashion editor on set during a photoshoot (according to a now-deleted Instagram post of that fashion editor). Irene took to the social media platform to post an official statement, admitting her wrongdoings, and apologizing for her behavior. SM Entertainment also subsequently released an apology for the hurtful words and behavior. The heated controversy had caused widespread reaction as it sparked larger conversations about the deep-rooted "gapjil" (갑질) culture in Korean society. Experts and spokespersons of various political movements in South Korea believed that much of the public outrage towards Irene stems from the country's reckoning with "gapjil" (or abusive conduct and bullying by people in positions of power or seniority), an issue that the country has been trying to eradicate and tone down. The perception of the general public in South Korea toward members of idol groups also came to light with regards to the incident, wherein women in particular are held to a higher standard compared to male artists when it comes to controversies. Following further numerous speculations in regards to the incident, staffers who had previously worked with Irene voiced their opinion to defend the musician. Some stylists, dancers, and make-up artists that worked with her had also posted on their Instagram accounts that they had never experienced such rude actions that are being shared about Irene. The staffs shared that Irene is someone who has a clear understanding of what she wants and has the talent to deliver her opinions clearly; she also knows how to appreciate her staff through giving handwritten cards and gifts to staff members. Ellena Yim, a former SM stylist and visual director, also claimed there are always "two sides to every story" and it's unfortunate that people refused to look at the other side of the story as they only concentrate on what has been revealed and what they want to see. The involved fashion editor also spoke up about rumors circulating online and asked to stop the speculations. She emphasized that there was no monetary settlement, and only an exchange of "sincere apologies" occurred when they had met again.</longDescription>
      <date>27/07/2021</date>
      <image>img\6.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="8">
      <title>Bae Suzy</title>
      <category>Singer</category>
      <sortDescription>Bae Su-ji (Korean: 배수지; born October 10, 1994), better known as Bae Suzy, is a South Korean singer, actress and model. She was a member of the girl group Miss A under JYP Entertainment. She made her debut as an actress with television series Dream High (2011) and has gone on to appear in series such as Gu Family Book (2013), Uncontrollably Fond (2016), While You Were Sleeping (2017), Vagabond (2019) and Start-Up (2020). She made her film debut in Architecture 101 (2012). Since her successful film debut, she has been hailed as "The Nation's First Love" in her home country.</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>In October 2010, Bae became the fixed host for MBC Show! Music Core alongside Minho and Onew, both members of Shinee, and Jiyeon, of T-ara. Bae later hosted other events such as the Seoul Music Awards, Golden Disc Awards, and Mnet 20's Choice Awards where she won an award under the category "Hot New Star of 2011".Suzy at Hallyu Dream Concert, 3 October 2011
Apart from her group activities, Bae also ventured into acting. She made her acting debut in the music teen drama Dream High, which aired on KBS from January 3 to February 28. She also released an OST for the drama, titled "Winter Child". The drama was a local success, earning high viewership ratings during its two-month run; and also gained popularity in other countries. At the KBS Drama Awards, Bae won the Best New Actress award as well as Best Couple award with co-star Kim Soo-hyun. Bae also became a cast member in KBS TV reality show Invincible Youth 2. The show began filming its first episode on October 19 and aired on November 11.Bae made her film debut with Architecture 101 (2012) playing the younger version of the female protagonist. Architecture 101 was one of the ten most-watched films in Korea in the first quarter of 2012, and achieved over 4.1 million admissions nine weeks after its theater release; a new box-office record set for Korean melodramas. The same year, Bae played a supporting role in KBS drama Big, written by the Hong sisters, alongside Gong Yoo and Lee Min-jung.Bae was the first Korean female celebrity to win a singer rookie award, drama rookie award, film rookie award, and variety rookie award. She received the Best New Actress award at the 48th Baeksang Arts Awards for her acting performance in Architecture 101. On December 22, 2012, Bae won the Best Newcomer award in the Variety category at the KBS Entertainment Awards for her stint in Invincible Youth 2 In 2013, she starred in the historical fusion drama Gu Family Book alongside Lee Seung-gi. She received acting recognition at the MBC Drama Awards, winning the Top Excellence award and at the Seoul International Drama Awards, winning the Outstanding Actress award. She also featured on the variety show Healing Camp, becoming the youngest guest on the show.</longDescription>
      <date>04/08/2021</date>
      <image>img\7.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="9">
      <title>Tzuyu</title>
      <category>Singer</category>
      <sortDescription>Chou Tzu-yu (Chinese: 周子瑜, born 14 June 1999), known mononymously as Tzuyu (Korean: 쯔위, Korean pronunciation: ɯ.ɥi), is a Taiwanese singer based in South Korea. She is the youngest and the only Taiwanese member of the girl group Twice, formed by JYP Entertainment.</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>In November 2015, Tzuyu appeared with Twice on the Korean variety show My Little Television. She introduced herself as Taiwanese and held the flag of Republic of China (Taiwan) alongside that of South Korea. Mainland Chinese internet users reacted angrily towards Tzuyu's actions due to the political rift between the two countries. Soon after, Twice was barred from Chinese television and Tzuyu was pulled out of her endorsement with Chinese communications company Huawei. Meanwhile, her agency, JYP Entertainment, released a video showing Tzuyu reading an apology, which said in part:There is only one China, the two sides of the strait are one, and I have always felt proud to be Chinese. I feel extremely apologetic to my company and to Internet friends on both sides of the strait for the hurt that I have caused, and I also feel very guilty.Tzuyu's apology sparked a furore among the Taiwanese public on election day. The incident gained international attention as it was believed to have affected the 2016 Taiwanese general election. A survey found that Tzuyu's video apology affected the decision of about 1.34 million young voters.In response to criticism, JYP Entertainment announced that it would be adopting new procedures concerning its exports and overseas activities in order to protect employees from future controversies. This included the implementation of cultural sensitivity training for its artists and staff members. In an interview with The Korea Times, a JYP representative stated that the training would include issues pertaining to political conflicts between countries.</longDescription>
      <date>22/09/2021</date>
      <image>img\8.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="10">
      <title>Kim So-hyun</title>
      <category>Actress</category>
      <sortDescription>Kim So-hyun (Korean: 김소현; Hanja: 金所泫; born June 4, 1999) is a South Korean actress who began her career as a child in 2006, initially gaining public attention for playing pivotal roles in Moon Embracing the Sun (2012) and Missing You (2013).</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>She took on her first leading role in teen drama Who Are You: School 2015 (2015) and since then has starred in a musical Page Turner (2016), a historical melodrama The Emperor: Owner of the Mask (2017), a romantic comedy Radio Romance (2018), television dramas based on Naver Webtoon's Hey Ghost, Let's Fight (2016), Love Alarm (2019–2021) and The Tale of Nokdu (2019) and Korean folklore River Where the Moon Rises (2021). She was the regular host of MBC's music program Music Core and survival reality show Under Nineteen in 2019.Kim has been nicknamed by the Korean media as the "Nation's Little Sister", "Queen of Child Actresses", "Goddess of Historical Drama" and also the "Sageuk Goddess", after starring and appearing in various acclaimed historical period dramas throughout her career, and having gained experience working as an actress from childhood to the present day. She has established herself as a top Hallyu star. For her performance in River Where the Moon Rises, she was nominated for Baeksang Arts Award for Best Actress – Television, becoming one of the youngest nominees for the award.Kim consistently promotes her television work on Instagram. She was awarded the '2018 Most Grown Instagram Account' with 7.1 million followers. At the age of 21, Kim became the youngest South Korean actress to have more than 10 million followers on social media, alongside actor Lee Min-ho.</longDescription>
      <date>12/10/2021</date>
      <image>img\9.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="11">
      <title>Shin Ji-min</title>
      <category>Rapper</category>
      <sortDescription>Shin Ji-min (Korean: 신지민; born January 8, 1991), better known mononymously as Jimin, is a South Korean former rapper and singer. She was the leader and main rapper of the girl group AOA, which debuted in 2012 under FNC Entertainment. In 2015, Jimin was a semi-finalist in the first season of Unpretty Rapstar. During the show, she released several successful collaboration singles, most notably "Good Start" (with Seulong) and "Puss" (with Iron). Following allegations of bullying by former bandmate Kwon Mina, Jimin left the group and retired from the entertainment industry in July 2020.</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>In early 2015, Jimin was part of the variety show Unpretty Rapstar, a spin-off of Show Me The Money. Unpretty Rapstar is a female rappers survival program. The show consists of a single-elimination competition through rap performances. During the show, Jimin released a few collaboration singles, such as "T4SA" with MC Meta and Nuck. Her song with Seulong, "Good Start", was produced by Verbal Jint and peaked at number two on the Gaon Singles Chart. "Puss", her rap battle song with rapper Iron during the semi-finals, peaked at number one on the Gaon Singles Chart. She was also a cast member of the variety show Off to School for four episodes, beginning March 17, 2015.On April 28, Jimin and J.Don released the collaboration single "God". The song was produced by Rhymer of Brand New Music as part of FNC Entertainment's N Project. The song's music video was based on Game of Thrones.Jimin debuted as a soloist on March 3, 2016, with the single "Call You Bae", featuring Exo's Xiumin. The single is the first release of Jimin's solo project #OOTD (Outfit of the Day).In October 2017, Jimin released the single "Hallelujah", a Latin-pop influenced dance track, a collaboration with magazine W Korea.Jimin sung the OST for tvN's A Korean Odyssey together with Seo Yu-na, the song is called "If You Were Me" and it was released on January 28, 2018.On July 3, 2020, former AOA member Kwon Mina alleged in an Instagram post that Jimin had bullied her for a decade, which led to Kwon's withdrawal from the group in May 2019.  She posted a photo of her scarred wrist and claimed to have attempted suicide as a result of the bullying. Jimin reportedly responded to the accusations by posting the word "fiction" to her Instagram Stories before deleting it shortly after. Kwon criticized the post, stating, "Fiction? It's too scary to say it's fiction." The allegations led to Jimin's departure from the group and the halt of all her activities in the entertainment industry.On January 13, 2022, FNC Entertainment announced that Jimin's contract with the company has expired.</longDescription>
      <date>05/11/2021</date>
      <image>img\10.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="12">
      <title>Moonbyul</title>
      <category>Rapper</category>
      <sortDescription>Moon Byul-yi (Korean: 문별이, born December 22, 1992), better known by the mononym Moonbyul, is a South Korean rapper, singer, songwriter, dancer, and radio host signed under RBW. She is the main rapper of the South Korean girl group Mamamoo. In May 2018, Moonbyul made her debut as a solo artist, releasing the digital single "Selfish".</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>Moon Byul-yi was born in Bucheon, Gyeonggi-do, South Korea, and is the oldest of three sisters. She decided to become a singer after watching TVXQ "Rising Sun" perform in 2005. She was accepted into Paekche Institute of the Arts for media music and vocals in 2011.Moonbyul debuted as a member of Mamamoo in June 2014. In May 2018, she debuted as a solo artist with the single "Selfish", featuring Seulgi of Red Velvet. She released her debut EP, Dark Side of the Moon, on February 14, 2020.She released her second EP, 6equence, on January 19, 2022. Before the album's release, she released the pre-release single "G999", featuring Mirani, on December 13, 2021, and released another pre-release single "Shutdown" on December 30, 2021.</longDescription>
      <date>22/11/2021</date>
      <image>img\11.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="13">
      <title>Shin Se-kyung</title>
      <category>Actress</category>
      <sortDescription>Shin Se-kyung (Korean: 신세경; born July 29, 1990) is a South Korean actress, singer and model. She started as a child actress and had her breakthrough in 2009 with the sitcom High Kick Through the Roof. Since then she starred in the films Hindsight (2011), R2B: Return to Base (2012) and Tazza: The Hidden Card (2014), as well as the television series Deep Rooted Tree (2011), The Girl Who Sees Smells (2015), Six Flying Dragons (2015–2016), The Bride of Habaek (2017), Black Knight: The Man Who Guards Me (2017–2018), Rookie Historian Goo Hae-Ryung (2019) and Run On (2020).</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>Shin made her entertainment debut at eight years old in 1998 when she was featured on the cover and poster for Seo Taiji's solo album Take Five. As a child actress, Shin Se Kyung was already known to the Koreans for her appearance in the popular children show Ppo Ppo Ppo, which also starred Big Bang's G-Dragon, she spend her childhood hosting children shows.After a small part in My Little Bride, she subsequently had starring roles in Cinderella, omnibus films Acoustic and Five Senses of Eros, as well as a well-received turn as the younger version of Princess Cheonmyeong in Queen Seondeok.Shin failed to gain a large following until her breakthrough role as a housemaid on the second season of the popular TV sitcom High Kick! in 2009. Building on her sitcom fame, Shin signed on to numerous television commercials and print advertisement and even made her as one of the most sought celebrity endorser. Lead roles in high-profile acting projects followed, among them film noir Hindsight with Song Kang-ho, the highly rated historical drama Deep Rooted Tree with Jang Hyuk and Han Suk-kyu, and aerial action film R2B: Return to Base with Rain.However, Shin's next project Fashion King (2012) was poorly received by audiences, particularly its controversial ending. Shin then released her first digital single, "You Were Sweet," which she recorded to promote a coffee franchise she models for. A former singer trainee in middle school, Shin has also contributed songs to the soundtrack of Hindsight, the charity album Love Tree Project, and did her own singing in showcase piece Acoustic. In 2012, she recorded a Christmas carol duet with Epitone Project.Shin returned to television in the 2013 melodrama When a Man Falls in Love opposite Song Seung-heon, but she received criticism from viewers for her passive character. In 2014, she played a more "bold and confident" role in the gambling film Tazza: The Hidden Card, followed by the fantasy-action series Blade Man.</longDescription>
      <date>10/12/2021</date>
      <image>img\12.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="14">
      <title>Seo Yu-na</title>
      <category>Singer</category>
      <sortDescription>Seo Yu-na (Hangul: 서유나; born December 30, 1992), better known by the mononym Yuna, is a South Korean singer, actress and yoga instructor. She is a former member of the South Korean girl group AOA and its sub-groups, AOA Black and AOA Cream.</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>On 30 July 2012, Yuna made her debut as a member of AOA on Mnet's M! Countdown with their debut single album, Angels' Story and the title track "Elvis". AOA has released three EPs and nine singles as of 22 June 2015. She is part of AOA's subunit "AOA Black". In 2015, AOA traveled to Hainan where they filmed One Fine Day, a variety program in which idols/idol groups go on a "healing" vacation. They were the seventh idol group to appear on the program(followed by Girl's Day)tation neededYuna is also part of sub-unit AOA Cream together with Shin Hye-jeong and Kim Chanmi. The sub-unit released their first teaser on 1 February 2016. The music video teaser for title track I'm Jelly Baby was released on 4 February 2016. AOA Cream released their title track together with the MV on 12 February 2016.On 1 January 2021, Yuna's contract expired with FNC Entertainment, and she left the company.Yuna has also had a successful, yet lesser known acting career, as she has played a lead role in the Japanese Musical "Summer Snow" in 2013, as well as playing another lead role in the comedic Korean web-drama "Prince's Prince" in February 2015.On 20 October 2013, Yuna sang for the OST "I'm Ok" for KBS's TV series Marry Him If You Dare. The song "I'm OK" is the theme song for the main character Na Mi-rae.In October 2016 it was announced that she will be part of the cast of a new web-drama Hot and Sweet playing Joon Young, a part-time food worker. The drama will premiere on October 20 and run for 8 episodes. Yuna also released 2 songs for the drama, one "Hot and Sweet" a duet with Choi Min-hwan and "Everything" a solo song.In 2016, Yuna has also been cast in another new web-drama 'My Old Friend'. The drama will be aired starting in mid November for 5 episodes through Naver TVCast.In 2017, Yuna was cast in the romantic comedy series Single Wife, scheduled for August 23. In June 2017, she sang the theme song for drama My Only Love Song, the song is called "Another You".Yuna sung the OST for tvN's A Korean Odyssey together with Shin Ji-min, the song is called "If You Were Me" and it was released on January 28, 2018.In 2019 Yuna together with Shin Hye-jeong and Kim Chanmi will take part in Lifetime's reality program AOA DaSaDanang Heart Attack Danang where the members will travel to Danang, Vietnam for an adventure. In July 2019, Yuna was cast in web drama Love Formula 11M as So-jin.</longDescription>
      <date>25/01/2022</date>
      <image>img\13.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
   <blog id="15">
      <title>Yerin</title>
      <category>Singer</category>
      <sortDescription>Jung Ye-rin (Korean: 정예린; born August 19, 1996), known mononymously as Yerin (Korean: 예린), is a South Korean singer and actress. She is a former member of the South Korean girl group GFriend.Yerin was born on August 19, 1996, in Incheon. She attended the School of Performing Arts Seoul and graduated in 2015.</sortDescription>
      <longDescription>In January 2015, Yerin officially debuted as a member of GFriend with their first extended play, Season of Glass. She made her acting debut two months later playing a supporting role in the web drama Midnight's Girl. On April 13, 2015, she appeared in Super Junior Heechul and TRAX Jungmo unit MD's music video "I Wish".In January 2016, Yerin was chosen as a new MC for SBS MTV's music program The Show, alongside Zhou Mi. On October 17, 2016, she featured the song "Future Boyfriend" with El Camino.In 2017, Yerin collaborated with Cao Lu and Kisum on the single "Spring Again". Later that year, she participated in SBS's reality-documentary show Law of the Jungle, featuring in the episodes in Komodo.In June 2021, Yerin signed with Sublime Artist Agency as a solo artist and actress.</longDescription>
      <date>27/01/2022</date>
      <image>img\14.jpg</image>
      <authorName>HLLT</authorName>
      <authorPosition>Admin</authorPosition>
      <authorImage>img\author.jpg</authorImage>
   </blog>
</blog_list>